Class of 1982 Records, 1978-[ongoing]
Smith College Archives
Class of 1982 Records
1978-[ongoing]
Smith College. Class of 1982.
RG 80 UUID:11555b6f-a43a-42ad-a3b6-2944e554f39a
3 boxes (1.25 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1982.
The Class of 1982 was the 104th graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1982 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1982, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1982 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- General 1978-1982 (Box 2280, Folder 1)
- Commencement 1982 (Box 2280, Folder 2)
- Commencement Speaker 1982 (Box 2280, Folder 3)
- Freshman Handbook 1978-1979 (Box 2280, Folder 4)
- Ivy Day 1982 (Box 2280, Folder 5)
- Last Chapel 1982 (Box 2280, Folder 6)
- New Faces 1978-1979 (Box 2280, Folder 7)
- Reunions 1982 (Box 2280, Folder 8)
- Reunions 1992 (Box 2280, Folder 9)
- Super Sundae Sunday 1979 (Box 2280, Folder 10)
- Yearbook (Box 2281)
  - General 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 1)
  - A 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 2)
  - Bab-Bat 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 3)
  - Bla-Bou 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 4)
  - Bra-Byn 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 5)
  - Caf-Cla 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 6)
  - Cle-Cur 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 7)
  - Dah-Dic 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 8)
  - Dig-Dw 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 9)
  - E 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 10)
  - Fa-Fl 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 11)
  - Fo-Fu 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 12)
  - Ga-Gi 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 13)
  - Gl-Gu 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 14)
  - Ha-Hen 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 15)
  - Hes-Ho 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 16)
  - I 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 17)
  - J 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 18)
  - Ka-Kel 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 19)
  - Ken-Kur 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 20)
  - La-Lef 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 21)
  - Len-Lu 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 22)
  - Ma-May 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 1)
  - Mc-Me 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 2)
  - Mf-My 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 3)
  - N 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 4)
  - O 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 5)
  - Pa-Pe 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 6)
  - Ph 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 7)
  - Po-Pu 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 8)
  - Q 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 9)
  - Ra-Ri 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 10)
  - Ro-Ru 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 11)
  - Sa-Sh 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 12)
  - Si-Sp 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 13)
  - Sr-Sv 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 14)
  - T 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 15)
  - U 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 16)
  - V 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 17)
  - Wa-We 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 18)
  - Wh-Wu 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 19)
  - Y 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 20)
  - Z 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 21)
- Candids 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 22)
- Christmas Season 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 23)
- Clubs-A-Ph 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 24)
- Clubs-Pr-Wr 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 25)
- Educational 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 26)
- Faculty 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 27)
- Houses 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 28)
- Houses and Buildings 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 29)
- Living 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 30)
- Not Used 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 31)
- Rally Day 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 32)
- Senators 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 33)
- Sports 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 34)
- Student Activities 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 35)